Morris, James O. Office Files /4055
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- AID - Chile Project Files and Reports. (Box 5)
  - Chile Final Report, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- International Labor Training Program.; New York State Labor History Association. Folders and papers are curling in box 6 (Box 6)
  - Bales, Mitzi - International Labor Training Program (ILTP), 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Goodwyn, Jack - ILTP, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Knight, Donald - ILTP, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mackin, Edward - ILTP, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Myrtue, Marvin - ILTP, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Savolainen, William - ILTP, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Includes a map of Finland in Finnish
  - Thalmayer, John - ILTP, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Townsend, Walter - ILTP, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    April 23, 1963
  - Valenciana, Clifford - ILTP, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO Mailing List - ILTP, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    September 27, 1962
  - Candidates, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    April 22, 1963
  - Conditions Governing Internship - ILTP, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO Recognition - ILTP, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Donovan Report - ILTP, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation - ILTP, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Final Evaluation - ILTP, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Final Evaluation - ILTP - Additional Copy, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Financial Statement - ILTP, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Fund for International Social and Economic Education, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Final Report - ILTP, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Group Photo of Second Group - ILTP (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Item is one black and white photograph, names of those photographs are written on the back
  - International Labor Training Program, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Internee Addresses - ILTP, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Lyons, Frank - ILTP, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Puerto Rico - ILTP, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Program for First Group - ILTP, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Marshall Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Scholarship Announcement - ILTP (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Doris Stevenson - ILTP, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Teaching English to Foreigners - ILTP, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Includes some English/French/Spanish material
  - Termination - ILTP, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    May 29, 1963
  - New York State Labor History Association Constitution and Bylaws, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - New York State Labor History Association, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - New York State Labor History (Addresses), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - New York State Labor History Association Second Annual Meeting, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - New York State Labor History Association Third Annual Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - New York State Labor History Association - 1979 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Labor History Pennsylvania Society, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Labor History Illinois Society, 1969-1978 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Includes several black and white photographs
  - Labor History Society Vermont-New Hampshire (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Item is one handwritten page
  - Labor Societies (Other), 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- UTU Project. (Box 7)
  - UTU (United Transportation Union) Project - General Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on National Railroad Historical Preservation, 1968-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholism Conference, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - UTU Project - Antique Dealers, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - UTU Project - Approval of Expenditure Forms, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Industrial Relations Project (RIRP) - Association of American Railroads, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bibliography of Industrial Relations in the Railroad Industry, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - RIRP - Brooks and Gamm, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - UTU Project - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1949-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - UTU Project - Budget (including negotiations), 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - RIRP - Buffalo Railroad Labor Studies Program, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - RIRP - Carrier Personnel Representatives, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - RIRP - Chicago and Northwestern, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - UTU Project - Congress of Railway Unions, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - RIRP - Con Rail, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - UTU Project - Correspondence pre-1973, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - UTU Project - Correspondence pre-1971, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - UTU Project - Department of Transportation, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - UTU Project - Federated Council of the International Association of Railway Employees (FCRE), 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - UTU Project - Fiscal, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - UTU Project - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMA), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - UTU Project - Information to Donors (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - UTU Project - Inter-Office Memos, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - UTU Project - Interview Sheet (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - RIRP - "Matters Pending" (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - UTU Project - Memos regarding Specific Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - UTU - Minutes of Meetings, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    august 8, 1972
  - Guidelines for Union Records Acquisitions (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Guidelines for Management and Government Records Acquisitions (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - UTU Project - Travel and Approval Forms, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - UTU Project - National Railway Labor Conference, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - UTU Project - News, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Entirely news clippings
  - UTU Project - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen (ORC and B), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - RIRP - Railroad Conference - ILR School, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - UTU Project - Railroad Contacts - Management, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - UTU Project - Railway Clerks, 1969-1975 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Railway Employees Department, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - UTU Project - Railway Labor, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - UTU Project - Railway Labor Executives' Association, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - UTU Project - Research Assistantship, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - UTU Project - RIRP Brochure (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - UTU Project - Space Projection, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    February 21, 1972
  - UTU Project - Staffing - Vita, etc., 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - UTU Project - United Transportation Union, 1971-1979 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - UTU Project - Youth Conference - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    October 15-18, 1972
  - Railway Project Report to Delegates, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Chile Files. (Box 8)
  - Programs in International Industrial Relations, 1957-1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Chile Project, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - ILR Organizations and University - National Institute for Labor Education (NILE), 1957-1963 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Workers' Education - Chile, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Workers' Education - Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores (ORIT), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Workers' Education - Philippines, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Puerto Rico - Labor Relations Institute, 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Chile - University of Chile - INSORA Personnel, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - ILR Organizations - Colombia - National University, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Latin America - Cornell ILR Bibliography Project, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - International Labor Organization (ILO) - Conference in Chile, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    March 5-19, 1962
  - ILO - Montevideo ILR Conference, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    November 3-12, 1960
  - University and ILR Organizations - Chile - Centro de Estudios Sindicales (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Items are two brochures, entirely in Spanish
  - University and ILR Organizations - Chile - Graduate Program, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Chile - University of Chile Extension, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Includes mostly Spanish language material; includes news clippings
  - University and ILR Organizations - Chile - University of Chile - Department of Labor Relations (DLR) - Barria Project, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Chile - University of Chile - DLR - Union Leaders Project, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - University and ILR Organizations - Chile - University of Chile - INSORA Technical Studies, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Coal Miners, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Confederacion de Empleadoes de Industrias y Comercio, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Federacion Santiago Watt (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Confederacion Maritima de Chile (COMACH), 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Sindicato Prof. de la Industria Ganadera, 1911-1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Sindicato Industrial de Puente Alto, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Central Unica de Trabajadores de Chile (CUT), 1953-1961 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Organization y Administracion Sindical, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Steel Workers, 1953-1959 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - CEPCH (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Agrupacion Nacional de Empleados Fiscales (ANEF), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Confederacion de Trabajadores del Cobre, 1956-1961 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Entirely Spanish language material; includes 9 black and white photographs
  - Federaciones de Trabajadores Textiles, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Asociacion Nacional de Empleados de la Superintendencia de Abastecimientos y Precios, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Historia del Movimiento Sindical, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Codigo de Trabajo, 1949-1958 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Dirigentes (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Ley de Retiro, Num. 447 del 15 de Mayo de 1951 y Leyes Relacionadas Con Esta, 1951-1955 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Confederacion Latino-Americana de Sindicalistas Cristianos (CLASC), 1956-1965 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Chilean Trade Union Association (ASICH), 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Entirely Spanish language material; includes news clippings
  - Conferencia Sindical Latino Americana (CSLA), 1927-1929 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Confederacion de Trabajadoras de America Latina (CTAL), 1938-1948 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Confederacion Unica de Trabajadores de la America Latina (CUTAL), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Pan-American Federation of Labor (PAFL), 1927 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Trade Secretariats - Postal, Telegraph, and Telephone International (PTTI), 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Chile Files - Drafts of Chile Labor Laws; Term Papers; National Archives; History of ILR School; Description on Sources for Legal and Social Science Research in Latin America; CLASC File Early Draft Plan - Inter-American School for Workers. (Box 9)
  - Chile - Labor Education Programs I, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Chile - Labor Education Programs II, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Description of Sources for Legal and Social Science Research in Latin America, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    June 1970
  - Inter-American School for Workers - Early Draft Plan, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - History of ILR School, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    There is probably a typo on the page dated November 18, 1955; the year should be 1966
  - CLASC (Confederacion Latinoamericana de Sindicalistas Cristianos) File (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - National Archives, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Sindicato Industrial de Papeleros de Puente Alto, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Term Papers by Chilean Students, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Term Papers by Chilean Students - Additional Materials, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Project on Chilean Labor and Union Law - Early Sources, 1900-1920 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Project on Chilean Labor and Union Law - Later Sources, 1924-1928 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Drafts of Labor Laws of Chile, 1952-1960 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Chile Files. Accion Sindical Chilena, ASiCh. (Box 10)
  - ASICH - Molina, Chile (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to ASICH and other Labor Leaders, 1953-1959 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Chile - Camara de Diputados, 1948-1966 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Archivo de Volantes, Circulares de Obispos, Audiciones Radiales, Publicaciones etc. - Sobre Cuestion Social, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Entirely Spanish language material; mostly news clippings
  - Los Sucesos de Molina, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Material ASICH Molina, 1953-1955 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - ASICH and Acta de la Sesion de 1958, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - ASICH Miscellany, 1954-1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Almost entirely Spanish language material, includes some French material
  - Central Cristiana de Trabajadores - ASICH, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Direccion General del Trabajo, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Conflicto Colectivo, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Inspector Departamental del Trabajo, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Reports and Letters, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Entirely Spanish language material; handle folder with caution, several items have a large number of rusty staples sticking out
- Introduction I, 1935-1959 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Project notes and sources
- Introduction II, 1956-1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Project notes and sources; includes news clippings
- Part 1, 1906-1919 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Project notes and sources; includes some Spanish language material
- Industrial Relation System, 1948-1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- PD and PSO, 1911-1951 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Almost entirely handwritten material; project notes and sources
- Chapter 1 - Introduction - Present IR System, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Project notes and sources, includes some Spanish language material; includes news clippings
- Employer Opposition in the 1930s, 1932-1942 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Project notes and sources; includes mostly Spanish language material
- Final Conclusion (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Entirely handwritten material; project notes and sources
- Conclusion Chapter 10, 1958-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Chapter 3, 1948-1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- FOCH, Recabarren, and IWW - I (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Entirely handwritten material; project notes and sources; includes some Spanish language material
- FOCH, Recabarren, and IWW - II (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Mostly handwritten material; project notes and sources; includes mostly Spanish language material
- FOCH, Recabarren, and IWW - III, 1919-1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Project notes and sources, includes some Spanish language material
- FOCH, Recabarren, and IWW - IV, 1913-1962 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Part 2, 1919-1936 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- The Conservative Project and the Intellectuals, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Mostly handwritten material; project notes and sources; includes some Spanish language material
- The Elite Opposition - I, 1919-1926 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- The Elite Opposition - II, 1915-1963 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Chapter 7 - I, 1925-1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Chapter 7 - II, 1929-1940 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Chapter 9, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- LR and Strikes, 1903-1907 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Additional Material for Unanticipated Consequences and Conclusion (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Not Used - I, 1909-1924 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Not Used - II, 1906-1965 (Box 11, Folder 25)